(Sheldon:)...by building an exact replica of Jerusalem
in the middle of the Mexican desert.
(Gablehouser:)To what end?
(Sheldon:)You know, it's like the baseball movie.
"Build it and they will come."
(Gablehouser:)Who will come?
(Sheldon:)The Jewish people.
What if they don't come?
(Sheldon:)We'll make it nice, put out a spread.
Okay, well, speaking of spreads...
...we're having a welcoming party
this afternoon for Mr. Kim...
- ...who's agreed to join us at the university.
- Of course he has.
(Sheldon:)The oracle told us little Neo was the one.
You can see the matrix, can't you?
Okay, well, obviously, you're very busy
with your, ah, um...
(Gablehouser:)Come, Dennis.
(Gablehouser:)You'll have to excuse Dr. Cooper.
He's been under a lot of, um...
(Gablehouser:)He's nuts.
[SHELDON HUMMING "CIELITO LINDO"]
[SINGING IN HEBREW]
(Sheldon(voice off, sings to a Mexican tune):)They'll come, they'll settle
And I'll win the prize